A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence with localities, 1942-1945., Extent: XX cubic feet (XX boxes). (Box XX)
  - Correspondence with locatilities, 1942.
    - Pittsylvania County
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Pocahontas (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Pound (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Powhatan County
      - General, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Portsmouth
      - General, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Prince Edward County
      - General, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Prince George County
      - General, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Prince William County
      - General, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Princess Anne County
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilziation, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Pulaski County
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Radford
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Rappahannock County
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Richlands (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Richmond County
      - General, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Richmond, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Rileysville (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke County
      - General, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - General - Insignia, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection - Blackouts, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rockbridge County
      - General, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Rockingham County
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Russell County
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Saltville (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Scott County
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Shenandoah (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Shenandoah County
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Smyth County
      - General, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - South Norfolk, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Southampton County
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Spotsylvania County
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Stafford County
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Stanley (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Staunton, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - St. Paul (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Stephens City (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Suffolk, City of
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - General - Publications, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Surry County
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Sussex County
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Tazewell County
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - General - Negro activities, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Tazewell (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Beach (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Warren County
      - General, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Warwick County
      - General, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Washington County
      - General, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Waynesboro (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilizaiton, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Westmoreland County
      - General, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - West Point (town of)
      - General, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Williamsburg
      - General, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Winchester
      - General, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Wise County
      - General, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Wythe County
      - General, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - York County
      - General, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1942. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with locatilities, 1943-1945.
    - Accomack County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Albemarle County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Alexandria County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - General - Conference and meetings, 1943. (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - General - Publicity, 1943. (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - General - Service awards, 1943-1945. (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration (Richmond District), 1943. (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection - Masks and pennants, 1943. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Amelia County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Amherst County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Amonate, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943. (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Appalachia, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Appomattox County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Appomattox, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Arlington County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - General - Service awards, 1943-1945. (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943-1945. (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1945. (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1945. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Augusta County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Bath County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Bedford County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Big Stone Gap, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - General - Speakers Bureau, 1943. (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - General - Transportation, 1943. (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Bishop, Town of
      - General, 1943. (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Blacksburg, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Blackstone, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Bland County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Bluefield, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Botetourt County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Bristol, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - General - Conferences and meetings, 1943-1943. (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - General - Negro activities, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - General - Publications, 1943. (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Brunswick County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Buchanan County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Buckingham County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 26)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 27)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Buena Vista, City of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 62, Folder 29)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 30)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Burkeville, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Campbell County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Cape Charles, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Caroline County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Carroll County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Charles City County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Charlotte County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Charlottesville, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Chesterfield County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Christiansburg-Cambria, Town of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Clarke County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Clifton Forge, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Coeburn, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Colonial Heights, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Covington, Town of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - General - Publications, 1943. (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - General - Speakers Bureau, 1943. (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943. (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Craig County
      - General, 1943. (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Crewe, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Culpeper County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Cumberland County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Danville, City of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - General - Conferences and meetings, 1943. (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - General - Publications, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Nutrition, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Reports, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Dendron, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Dickenson County
      - General, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Dinwiddie County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Elizabeth City County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - General - Publications, 1943-1944. (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - General - Speakers Bureau, 1943. (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection - Training schools, 1943. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Essex County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943. (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal Equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Farmville, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Fauquier County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Floyd County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Fluvanna County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Franklin County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Franklin, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Frederick County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Fredericksburg
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - General - Conferences and meetings, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - General - Insignia, 1943-1944. (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Block plan, 1943. (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Admistration, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Bomb reconnaissance, 1943. (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection - Responsibility list, 1943. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Fries, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Galax, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Giles County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Gloucester County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 69, Folder 20)